LEVELS = [
  {
    problem: "John F. Kennedy",
    possible_answers: [40, 35, 32, 25],
    solution_quad: 2
  },
  {
    problem: "Harry S. Truman",
    possible_answers: [39, 20, 31, 33],
    solution_quad: 4
  }
  #{
    #problem: "sqrt(5! + 1)",
    #possible_answers: [121, 6, 9, 11],
    #solution_quad: 4
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "2 * 2 + 3 * 4 - 5",
    #possible_answers: [35, 11, -12, 23],
    #solution_quad: 2
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "3^2 * 2 - 4",
    #possible_answers: [14, 3, 77, -18],
    #solution_quad: 1
  #},
   #{
    #problem: "1^32 - 0!",
    #possible_answers: [1, 0, -1, 32],
    #solution_quad: 2
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "5! / 2! + 3!",
    #possible_answers: [72, 3.5, 66, 99],
    #solution_quad: 3
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "8 / 2! + 3 - 4",
    #possible_answers: [4, 3, 8, 0],
    #solution_quad: 2
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "11 - 7! / 6!",
    #possible_answers: [0.5, 10, 22, 4],
    #solution_quad: 4
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "10 - 2 * 8 + 8",
    #possible_answers: [96, 72, 2, 8],
    #solution_quad: 3
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "1 * 2 - 1 * 1 + 1",
    #possible_answers: [2, 3, 1, 0],
    #solution_quad: 1
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "(13^2 - 9) / (3! + 4)",
    #possible_answers: [9, 16, 12, 111],
    #solution_quad: 2
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "sqrt(4^2 + 3^2)",
    #possible_answers: [-7, -5, 7, 5],
    #solution_quad: 4
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "8 * 8 - (20 / 2)",
    #possible_answers: [44, 54, 32, 6.4],
    #solution_quad: 2
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "sqrt(3 * 9 + 3^2)",
    #possible_answers: [6, 4, 9, 7],
    #solution_quad: 1
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "(2! * 2!)^2",
    #possible_answers: [2, 4, 8, 16],
    #solution_quad: 4
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "6^2 / 3^2",
    #possible_answers: [6, 7, 4, 9],
    #solution_quad: 3
  #},
  #{
    #problem: "sqrt((3 * 4)^2)",
    #possible_answers: [12, 6, 11, 13],
    #solution_quad: 1
  #}
]
